<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Find my ramblings catalogued here</title>
    <link>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Find my ramblings catalogued here</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 22:19:16 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Is it really AI &#39;art&#39;?</title>
      <link>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/aigenart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 22:19:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/aigenart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Can a painting generated by a machine be called art? I would argue no.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not too long ago I was having a discussion on whether AI art should be labelled, and my thought was that labelling was a good thing because without the distinction it undermines the effort and investment that human artists makes. It is no different from labelling hand made textiles vs machined, or factory farmed chicken vs organic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muv Luv: Alternative</title>
      <link>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/mla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:32:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/mla/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tldr&#34;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shinji got in the robot but it took 35 hours and we had to listen to his every stray thought. This VN is the epitome of tell don&amp;rsquo;t show. Buy only if you are 14 and think an hour long internal monologue about obeying orders is deep. tbf you&amp;rsquo;re getting a lot of decent animations and a typical but not bad mecha anime story here, but I wish I could have spent those 30 hours playing a better visual novel that respects my time (the other 10 hours is pretty good tho).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Love or Die Trying</title>
      <link>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/flodt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 17:46:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/flodt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past year or two I&amp;rsquo;ve been recommended by a lot of people to give FLoDT a try, and I recently finally found the time to. The story was pretty predictable for the most part, and the characters just aren&amp;rsquo;t really given the time to develop. Art and music was rather forgettable. I also hate the fake choices the game give you, there&amp;rsquo;s a hundred of them and only like 3 actually matter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Life Alyx</title>
      <link>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/hla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 15:52:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/hla/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Half Life, but in VR, expect linear corridors and physics puzzles. That wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be so bad on its own, except the game forces you to scavenge for ammo and supplies so a third of your playtime is just searching drawers and shelves which gets boring pretty quick. This also means you don&amp;rsquo;t really get to have fun with your guns until the final chapters, which is a shame since the guns are pretty fun to use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XCOM Chimera Squad Review</title>
      <link>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/xcomcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 15:49:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://o4ugdf54plqu.github.io/blog2/public/posts/xcomcs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tldr&#34;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chimera Squad is for you if you save scummed in the other XCOM games so that nobody dies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;full-review&#34;&gt;Full Review&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If XCOM 2 is a full three course meal, then Chimera Squad is drive thru burger and fries. It&amp;rsquo;s not as deep or as fleshed out as 2, but sometimes you just want the burger. Chimera Squad is what happens when you take XCOM 2 and repackage it to be played in short bursts. Also there&amp;rsquo;s a snek lady for you to choke bad guys into submission.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
